Printable Generators and Tools

Popular Tools:

Privacy Policy
==============

The information provided by Printable Creative (“Company”, “Website”, “Site”, “I”, “we”, “our” or “us”) is dedicated to respecting the privacy of your personal information, and this privacy policy describes what information is collected from you on https://printablecreative.com (hereinafter the “website”) and how it is used. The term “you” refers to anyone who uses, visits and/or views the website.

By visiting and using the website, you accept and agree to be bound by this privacy policy. Your continued use of the website after posting of any changes to our Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes and updates. You must not access or use the website if you do not wish to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

### What Information We Collect and How It is Used

When you access the website, you may provide certain personally identifiable information including but not limited to your name, email address, phone number, address, avatar image, credit card information when you make a purchase on the website.

This information is collected when you register on the site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, contact us, use the search feature on the website, provide comments or any other feedback, fill out a form or use live chat or enter any other information on the website to communicate with us. From time to time, we may also collect information that you submit when you participate in any online surveys that we may post on our website.

Your personal information is used to personalize your experience, improve the website to better serve you, provide customer service support, efficiently process your requests or transactions, tailor advertisements to you, elicit reviews of services or products, provide you offers, promotions and to follow up with you through correspondence (email, live chat, or phone).

We may also use this information to provide you offers and promotions from our partners and/or our affiliates in exchange for a commission without additional cost to you.

Additionally, like other websites, this website automatically collects certain information about you through Log Data and Google Analytics. Log Data is information about your computer’s Internet Protocol Address, which is your “IP” address, browser information, Internet Service Provider’s information, your operating system, and your browser type. Similarly, Google Analytics collects certain information about your location, browsing history, the pages you visit, equipment you used to access the website, traffic patterns, and other general patterns related to your use of the website.

This information is used to analyze website statistics related to user behavior and interests, improve our performance and your use of the website and to further enhance our products and services offered to you.

### Social Media and Comments

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. When you leave a comment, your name, email address and website/organization name is not shared with a third party, and may be used to communicate with you.

Social media accounts and sharing options are available on this website. Social media sites (Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and so forth) can track your personal information. Should you choose to interact with us on social media, please note that you will be voluntarily disclosing that personal information. This information is no longer private. It becomes public information and can be collected and used by others. We have no control over and take no responsibility for the use, storage or dissemination of such publicly disclosed personal information by you.

Any such interactions via comments and social media with us do not subject us to any kind of liability related to misuse of your information by others.

### Use of Cookies

The website may use cookies to facilitate your use of the website. Cookies are files with small amounts of data including an anonymous unique identifier that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive when you are viewing the website. Just like other websites, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable information including but not limited to your IP address, geographic location, language preference, date and time of visitors.

When you leave a comment on our website, you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment.

If you have an account and you log in to this website, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

We may use cookies for various reasons such as optimizing and personalizing your browsing experience, checking our website analytics, saving your preferences and settings for future use, serving ads based on your liking and interests, affiliate marketing and for posting comments on our website.

This information is only collected to better serve and understand your user experience on the website.  You have the option of turning off cookies on your computer should you wish to do so. If you choose to do that, you may not be able to view all features and content of this website.

**Google Cookies Policy:** Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services.

For more details, please visit: https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads

As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

**Third Party Networks:** Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on our website, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that we have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### IP Addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

### Log Files

Like many other web sites, we also makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Use of Web Beacons and Pixels

In conjunction with the use of cookies, third parties may also use web beacons, which are also known as tracking bug, page tag, clear GIFs, web bugs or tracking pixel to collect general information about your use of our website. They are used to monitor user activity and track customer behavior data. This information may be relevant to third parties such as the ad networks used on our website to tailor the advertising based on your interests and behavior.

We may use social media pixels to track and collect general information about your use in compliance with different social media sites (Facebook, Twitter, etc) for the purpose of promoting products, tracking conversions, re-marketing, running target advertisements and so forth.

Third parties like Facebook may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect and receive information from our website for the purpose of providing target advertisements. You may see our ads on Facebook after you have visited our website.

### Third Party Links and Use

We may include, offer or advertise third party links, products or services on the website. Once you click on a third party link and leave this website, you are no longer bound by our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.

Articles on this website may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, advertisements, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

We may use Google Adsense advertising along with any other third party advertising on the website. Google is a third party that also uses cookies to serve ads on the website for the purpose of providing a positive user experience. You can opt out of Google by visiting their privacy policy.

We have no control over any of these third parties and they have their own privacy policies. Neither are we responsible for the activities and practices of these third parties. You should contact them directly and read their privacy policies for any questions. You also agree that your use of these third party websites is solely at your risk.

WE DO NOT WARRANT, ENDORSE, GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY INFORMATION OFFERED BY THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES LINKED THROUGH THE SITE OR ANY WEBSITE OR FEATURE LINKED IN ANY BANNER OR OTHER ADVERTISING. WE WILL NOT BE A PARTY TO OR IN ANY WAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR MONITORING ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.

### Sponsored Links, Affiliate Tracking & Commissions

Our website may contain adverts, sponsored and affiliate links on some pages. These are typically served through our advertising partners; Google Adsense, Amazon Affiliates, ShareASale or are self served through our own means. We only use trusted advertising partners who each have high standards of user privacy and security. However we do not control the actual adverts seen / displayed by our advertising partners. Our ad partners may collect data and use cookies for ad personalization and measurement. Where ad preferences are requested as ‘non-personalized’ cookies may still be used for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting and to combat fraud and abuse.

Clicking on any adverts, sponsored or affiliate links may track your actions by using a cookie saved to your device. You can read more about cookies on this website above. Your actions are usually recorded as a referral from our website by this cookie. In most cases we earn a very small commission from the advertiser or advertising partner, at no cost to you, whether you make a purchase on their website or not.

We use advertising partners in these ways to help generate an income from the website, which allows us to continue our work and provide you with the best overall experience and valued information.

If you have any concerns about this we suggest you do not click on any adverts, sponsored or affiliate links found throughout the website.

### Disclosure of Your Information

As a general rule, we do not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent with the exception of the following circumstances:

1. We may disclose your information to our trusted third parties that work with us such as our website hosting partners, email marketing service provider, other service providers that assist in the operation of the website, and any other affiliates and subsidiaries we rely upon to provide you products and services offered here.
2. We may disclose your information in order to comply with state or federal regulations related to copyright infringement lawsuits or any other legal claims related to the website.
3. We may disclose your information to our successor and/or acquiring party in the event of a merger, acquisition, restructuring, dissolution or partial sale in the future. However, your personal information will be transferred to the acquiring party in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Children’s Privacy and Data

We respect the privacy of children and “child” means an individual under the age of 13. All information and content on this website is intended for individuals over the age of 18. Children under the age of 13 are prohibited from using this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental or guardian consent. If you believe personal information is collected from someone under the age of 13 without parental or guardian consent, then please contact us to have that information deleted.

### Email Marketing and Policies

You have the option of opting in or unsubscribing from our email list. By subscribing and opting in, you agree to receiving newsletters, updates, messages, promotional materials and any other content related to this website. When you send an email, your email message along with email address and responses are saved for communication purposes with you. This information is kept confidential and we do not share, sell or trade your email information with third parties except as otherwise stated in this privacy policy.

We do not envision offering goods or services to individuals living in the European Union as outlined in the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).

If you are in the European Union and opt in to receive any of our free products or services and/or purchase any products or services through our website then you will be subscribed to receive our free email newsletter once you affirmatively consent to it. Please see **Opt Out** section below should you wish to “unsubscribe” and not receive any emails from us.

But if you are NOT in the European Union then you will be automatically subscribed to receive our free email newsletter once you opt in to receive any of our free products or services and/or purchase any products or services through our website. Please see **Opt Out** section below should you wish to “unsubscribe” and not receive any emails from us.

### **Choice /** Opt Out

We comply with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 and do not spam or send misleading information. Should you wish to no longer receive communication from us, you have the option of unsubscribing by clicking “unsubscribe” in the bottom of the email we send to you or by contacting us.

As for third party websites, please contact them directly to unsubscribe and/or opt out from their communications.

### GDPR Visitor Rights

Under the GDPR, if you are within the European Union, you are entitled to certain rights and information listed below.

We will retain any information you choose to provide to us until the earlier of:

1. You ask us to delete the information by sending a request to contact@printablecreative.com. Please note that such requests may result in you no longer being able to access paid or free content previously provided to you.
2. Our decision to cease using our existing data providers.
3. The Company decides to no longer be in business or continue to offer the services.
4. The data is no longer needed to provide you service, is too costly to maintain further retention, or the Company finds it outdated.

You have the right to request access to your data that we store and have the ability to access your personal data.

You have the rights to either rectify or erase your personal data. You have the right to verify the accuracy of your personal data and have it corrected or removed completely.

You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your data. When you restrict the processing of your data, we can store your data but cannot process it further.

You have the right to object to the processing of your data in certain circumstances including but not limited to direct marketing, profiling, scientific or historical research purposes, statistical purposes, automated decision making and profiling and tasks based on legitimate interests or in the public interest/exercise of official authority.

You have the right to the portability of your data. You have the right to request your personal data from us, receive it and transfer it to another controller.

You have the right to withdraw consent at any time. If you have provided consent to the Company’s processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent.

You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection Regulation.

We require only the information that is reasonably necessary to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.

### Your Rights Under The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA Compliance)

If you reside in California, you are entitled to additional rights under California law and we ensure compliance with the CCPA. Here are your rights:

1. You have the right to know whether your personal information is sold or disclosed to third parties.
2. You have the right to say no to the sale of your personal information.
3. You also have the right to access your personal information, which we will provide within 30 days of such request.
4. You have the right to know what personal information is collected from you and how it is used, which we explained in this Privacy Policy
5. You have the right to have your personal information deleted
6. You have the right to equal service, price and no discrimination
7. You have the right to data portability and right to request your personal information and use it for your own purposes

Pursuant to California’s “Shine the Light Act,” you are permitted to request information about the manner in which we share certain categories of information with third parties for their marketing use. We may disclose your personal information to our affiliates or other related third parties such as service providers, vendors for their use in marketing to you, so we can provide the products and/or services offered on this website to you. When we disclose such information, your personal information is still kept confidential and between us and that third party. It is not used for any other purpose that’s not permitted under the laws.

Please be advised we DO NOT SELL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION to third parties and have never sold your personal information. We do not intend to sell your personal information in the future either.

Under the CCPA, you still have the right to opt-out of such sales and send us a “do not sell my information” request. If you would like to exercise any of your rights under California law, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by sending us an email at contact@printablecreative.com. Only you as the person registered with the California Secretary of State can make such verifiable consumer requested related to your personal information or someone you authorize to act on your behalf.

Your verifiable consumer request must provide sufficient information that allows us to verify that you are the person you are claiming to be or that you are the authorized representative of such person about whom we had collected personal information. You must describe your request with enough details such as your first and last name, address and your country that allow us to properly understand the request and respond to it. Please note we cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information unless we first verify your identity or authority to make such a request and confirm that the personal information relates to you. We will make all attempts to respond to your request within 30 days of receipt.

This privacy notice for California residents supplements the information included in the previous sections of this privacy policy. California and Delaware law also requires us to state whether we honor “Do Not Track” settings in your browser regarding targeted advertising and we do not monitor or respond to Do Not Track browser requests.

### Affiliates Disclaimer

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn advertising fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated websites.

The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) requires that we disclose any relationship we have between a product manufacturer or service provider when we write about a product or service.

Here are the guidelines we operate under:

We participate in number of affiliate programs including Amazon, ShareASale. Links originating on our website that lead to product purchases to these Affiliate Programs generate affiliate revenue for us. If we create a link to a product or service in a review, sometimes we may get paid a commission if you purchase the product or service. It will be disclosed that in the review. The posts are never composed for the purpose of advertising.

The views expressed in our reviews are always the personal views of our team members and written for the sole purpose of informing our readers accurately.

We sometimes accept and publish sponsored posts, which is clearly highlighted as sponsored advertising. These are advertising products and all the opinions are always my own or my team member’s.

We also accept paid advertising on our website and use affiliate links in posts when they are available.

No advertiser will ever influence the content, topics or posts made in this site.

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us.

### Data Security and Protection

The security of your personal information is important to us, and we strive to follow generally commercial industry standards to protect your personal information submitted to us voluntarily and automatically. However, no method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee absolute security of your information.

When you make a credit card purchase or purchase through any means on the website, you will be directed to a third party vendor to complete the transaction. Any information you provide during the checkout process is not stored on our website but instead provided to the third party vendor that completes the purchase transaction.

By using this website, you agree to hold us harmless for any security breach and for any unauthorized use of your personal information by third parties. You also agree that we cannot be held responsible for any disclosure of your information through our website without our knowledge and consent.

### Website Disclaimer

The information provided by us is for general informational purposes only. All information on the Site and our mobile application is provided in good faith, however we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability or completeness of any information on the Site or our mobile application. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE SHALL WE HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF THE SITE OR OUR MOBILE APPLICATION OR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE AND OUR MOBILE APPLICATION. YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND OUR MOBILE APPLICATION AND YOUR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION ON THE SITE AND OUR MOBILE APPLICATION IS SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.

### Policy Changes

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. You are responsible for visiting this page periodically to check for future updates to this policy. Any modifications to this privacy policy will be effective upon our publishing of the new terms, and your continued use of our website after the posting of any updates constitutes your acceptance of our modified privacy policy.

### Consent

You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.

Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.

Copyright © 2024, PrintableCreative. All Rights Reserved.
